[Music]
I'm in South Korea a food lovers
Paradise for the next 11 days we're
going on an ultimate Korean food road
trip we'll drive over 1,500 km and get
way off the beaten path to discover some
of the most unique this might be one of
the first meals I've ever had that
requires a back ho
surprising wow that's a lot of heat the
ultimate hyom Maniac cooking addictive
flavor that you just cannot stop eating
and delicious foods in all of South
Korea considered the most ugly fish in
Korea and making it one of the most
tastiest dishes you can possibly imagine
and to taste what just might be my new
favorite Korean
food oh and a whole bucket of broth
those are the ribs with the bone
cage get ready for the most
mouthwatering Korean food
Adventure
[Music]
this a truly magical meat eating
experience they do it all in front of
you long drives in the van and some
behind the scenes of some things that
didn't quite go as
planned so this is a special formula
Korean beverage for helping you digest
who oh
no I'm Mark wans join me as we eat our
way through South Korea
[Music]
[Applause]
okay we made it welcome to inan welcome
to South
Korea C the overnight flight from
Bangkok uh landed this morning in inan
International Airport bright and early I
think we landed at about 6:30 7 a.m. uh
so definitely a little sleepy but really
happy to be here and I think I've been
to Korea I mean at least Soul maybe
three or four times but this food trip
to South Korea is going to be
different for the next 10 actually maybe
11 days we're going to
be food touring and road tripping
through the entire South Korean
Peninsula and that's going to be the the
van that we're
in
[Music]
okay most of the time when I've come to
Soul or actually landed at inan then I
take the train directly into Soul which
takes about an hour but it's nice to
have a a van this time driving and so we
stopped somewhere in this town kind of
halfway between and we're going to stop
for breakfast somewhere for a beef bones
what's the name of the dish uh he
okay oh one of the great things about
Korean food that I always love is just
how scorching hot it's always served and
Earth and stone stone bowls but this is
the hangover hangover soup um which
there are many different variations here
they have a sort of a beef a beef
version there's noodles in it there's
lots of Napa cabbage beef beef blood
leaks some chili on it as well as some
chili already added into it oh this
smells really good there's all of the
noodles in there which looks like the
maybe sweet potato
noodles
[Music]
so good okay and then we've got some of
the the radish
kimchi really crisp nice and
sour aged ripened oh it's
good and let's try one of the
chilies M oh really
crispy not that hot a little bit
hot oh man there's definitely a a lot of
wisdom and a reason why they call it
hangover stew in Korea it really does
cure your hangover but not only hangover
I think it's the perfect meal after you
get off of an airplane uh your airplane
hangover oh that's I just just feel
totally rejuvenated that was so good
next quick stop before we get back in
the van and head to
se this place is called a Tome
[Music]
place that's hot okay from here we're
driving back to Soul or to Soul uh
should be about an hour and 15
minutes
[Music]
okay oh again welcome to Soul South
Korea great to be here and nice room
what A View From the room but before we
get started I do want to say a huge
thank you to the Korean tourism board
for arranging for sponsoring my entire
trip here however they really wanted to
work with me and we designed an
itinerary we uh researched seed the food
together and it's all going to be
authentic it's all going to be extremely
local South Korean food that we go to um
and the food that we experience we've
got a small team with us arranged by the
Korea tourism organization who are
extremely helpful in setting up
restaurants taking care of travel
Logistics and helping me finish all the
food that being said today was just the
Arrival Day and it's a off day it's a
resting day it's not really a filming
day so we're going to probably get some
rest take a nap and then definitely do a
little bit of maybe just walking around
browsing around probably some eating in
the afternoon but the actual journey and
all of the delicious food and you're not
going to want to miss any of it is going
to begin tomorrow
morning oh yes so had a little bit of a
nap this afternoon and then we just
walked down the street to one of the
closest Korean barbecue restaurants just
down the road from where we're staying
uh ordered up some Korean beef oh yes oh
it's good to be back good to be back
here can't wait to have some
beef okay okay come s me that oh man
great family service here I love this
place oh and we got a just a few side
dishes cuz there's actually another
place I want to go check out to eat
after
this
oh that beef melts in your
mouth oh let me try that that
Rice
that was a really good barbecue just
classic simple old school style from
here let's go eat a
chicken we're in this area of town which
is called yongan and it's actually not
that far away it should just be about a
10 or 15 minute train ride away but we
need to go to the station take the train
and we'll be there
soon we found
it yongan
station and we are going to H
Hanam okay we made it and I think this
is actually part of the Korean railroad
not the the Metro but we just have three
stops we made it this is where the
restaurant is at Hanam
station oh oh nice oh this is the
rotisserie oh it's all burning wood too
all wood fire this is the this is the
cabinet of the the rotisserie chickens
they're they're small chicken stuffed
with with glutenous rice with ginang
with garlic smells incredible and what's
amazing is they burn only over wood wood
fire just sizzling away this must be 50
chickens in here at
once so the chickens are already
roasting outside so as soon as you sit
down literally within a minute the
chicken is at your table I looks so good
I love how simple it is everything's on
your table oh and by the way cheers oh
Ying Ying cheers come by come
by okay cannot wait to dig into that
chicken oh this is so this is all the
the chicken breast on the
outside oh it's smells so incredibly
good the garlic the ginang on the inside
oh it just look at the way it just
completely tears apart oh man I don't
even what should we start with maybe
just grab the drumstick the
drumstick oh it's
beautiful it
completely oh that's
hot oh man
it is so
tender just completely falls off the
bone the bone is just completely
clean and that first but and the taste
of the chicken is so creamy so flavorful
infused with the ginsing and the garlic
and the roasting fire it's not even
salty I mean we haven't even explored
all these sauces but that's tasty that
is delicious one of the things that
you'll notice especially with Korean
fried chicken with Chicken in Korea you
always get radish so chase that with
radish and let's Explore More of the
chicken let's move into the the sticky
rice or the glutenous rice which is
stuffed into the cavity you see jinang
in there the garlic you smell the garlic
you can see it's kind of yellow because
it's absorbed all of the chicken fat as
well oh yes oh wow is that a maybe a
j okay
wow do not take a huge bite of
that it is still on fire with the
chicken and that is
a tastes like a plum maybe one of those
Korean plums
um has a little bit of sweetness but
then at the same time that sweetness has
been released into the chicken man that
that sticky Rush is so good such a fun
food to eat as well just tearing apart a
whole chicken every bite could have skin
you would be happy as well this skin is
so good let's try that red
sauce oh it's also really sticky
perfect chicken was really nice really
relaxing we're going to head back to the
hotel from here uh so going to get some
rest and start fresh
tomorrow
so we are beginning this barbecue tour
at a place it's called Jo o and it is
one of the oldest Korean barbecue
restaurants in Soul and they specialize
in what is one of the most popular forms
Meats of Korean barbecue at a lot of
Korean barbecue restaurants you know you
cook it yourself at the table but here
you don't they cook it in the back this
is the old school we way where the chef
is cooking everybody's meal grilling
everybody's meat and then it's delivered
to you at your table they Grill it so
precisely then they keep tossing on like
this cup of the sauce and from what also
what I was reading that sauce their
recipe has not changed in over 80
years can't wait to try
it try a piece
first
[Music]
well the flavor keeps on coming as you
keep on chewing it's not like melting
your mouth tender it has some muscle
some texture to it but I think that way
in the muscle fiber it's just able to
absorb all of that flavor oh it's so
flavorful I think I'll grab a whole bone
this time oh you can see how juicy it is
I'll dip it into the bean paste I think
it's a type of Korean bean paste oh you
can see how that just wobbles
oh yes can't wait to try this
Bon oh wow what a spot and it's still
family run they're extremely friendly I
mean this is a preservation of Korean
barbecue
Heritage to continue with this barbecue
tour Korean barbecue tour we are at the
next place welcome to the maang meat
market this is the central meat
distribution Market so as soon as you
arrive here you can smell the aroma of
raw
[Music]
meat we're going to a place that's
called inang hanu this restaurant is
particularly famous for their water
aging so they take the hanu they vacuum
seal it and then they submerge it underw
and this sign up here says it's aged for
336 hours so we got the two trays of
beef it's unbelievably fatty and marbled
and you can see the difference between
the two plates this one is the Mixed
Plate fresh beef non-aged this one you
can see the the color turns darker the
muscle fiber starts to break down that
water aging process two weeks water aged
these are huge Saks actually
wow
wow that
marble putting on another one too but
the first water AED steak is ready hanu
which I cannot wait to
try
wow oh that melt in your
mouth oh man that's so much
flavor it's so fatty just melts in your
mouth but at the same time you feel the
muscles and the fibers of the beef for
my next piece let's try to dip in some
of the salt and some of the toppings a
little bit of Wasabi a little bit of
salt one of the favorite ways to eat
this kind of quality
beef oh wow
there's a waterfall of juice in my mouth
just liquefies on your tongue oh with
the salt that's incredible you got the
crunch of that salt a little bit of
sesame seeds in there and then the
Wasabi is so mild it just kind of like
is actually sweet doesn't go up your
nose at all wow that's rich what a meal
I love the texture the marbling just the
fat and juiciness of that water-aged Han
wo and it was also great to just spend
some time hanging out with friends in
Soul Korean Hano beef is some of the
best beef on Earth and Grilling up a
feast right within the market makes it
even more special insan hanu just might
live up to its name the best hanu of
your
[Music]
life today we're going to three
legendary restaurants in Soul back to
back then we'll drive a couple of hours
to Yan for a spicy dinner that I can't
can't wait to try and here we are at the
first place step out of the car and no
joke you could just smell the kimchi in
the air okay this place it has a
complicated name I'm I think I'm just
going to let jinu say it place called
Kim now typically I've always had the
kimchi stew with pork but they also have
a version with tuna and a version with
Spam I got to try the spam oh they
really have a system down and again
kimchi jig is all about the kimchi the
kimchi is what makes or breaks kimchi
jig so they're not making any mistakes
with the kimchi here they have a huge
pan of the kimchi um that first goes
into the pan then he adds in uh some
chili some garlic some other seasonings
some onions that goes into your pan from
there you choose your protein of choice
whether that be pork whether that be
tuna whether that be spam and then it
goes onto the the burner and then she
adds in some of the broth and then that
boils away until it just all combines
with the juices with the kimchi
expertly smells so good I'm going in so
this one is the classic the original
with pork kimchi chili pepper flakes
onions in here oh man it smells so good
oh
wow
oh oh that's hot oh it's still on fire
oh it's so good m
you know because it's all about kimchi
the kimchi is what makes or break the
kimchi jig and because kimchi is a a
fermented food there's such a varying
range of flavors and tastes and how
fermented it is and how fresh it is um
can have a huge impact on the flavor of
this dish okay the next version that I
just absolutely had to try is the spam
version big cubes of spam kimchi tofu in
here all the same ingredients just
massive cubes of
spam
oh okay got to admit that's really tasty
and I mean spam is something I grew up
eating a lot of when I was a kid
especially as my my mom is from Hawaii
Spam is also very popular in Hawaii so
that just immediately brings back the
good memories but then wrapped up in
this Kim juice stew gives it another
dimension that's like a a Spam sponge of
kimchi and one more thing before we
leave it's a huge honor if you look
around you'll see the the lids of the
the copper pans that they serve the
kimchi jig in which they have people
sign them and put them on the wall so
it's a huge
[Music]
honor man that kimchi jig was
outstanding fantastic on the next level
one of the best bowls I've ever had
highly recommended and we are moving on
to the next
food okay here we are at the next place
and check this out it's valet and they
have an entire power parking lot this is
all their parking they have a 10-story
parking garage all to themselves that's
all valet that's how popular it is we
are here for the next place oh this
restaurant is extremely popular almost
continuously a line especially if you
come in the peak Meal Time there'll be a
line coming out the the door and they've
been featured you can see here they've
just been featured in almost every news
station every TV station for their food
especially for their ningan the
buckwheat
noodles vinegar
yeah
mustard
wow
oh oh
skills that was amazing he's a true
connoisseur an expert at the ningan I
cannot wait to dig in all right here we
go so I
don't oh the texture of those buckweat
noodles is
incredible they're not as chewy as some
vergins that I've had
but you really taste the flavor the
buckweat the
meatiness it's so cold and refreshing so
good yeah he's good okay I'm going to
try some of the the bi
Nan
M mhm
this one is good as well it tastes the
sweet flavor of the goou tongue a little
bit of chili in there and then it has a
sesame oil nutty flavor to it yeah and
then you taste the flavor of the daon
the radish in there as well pieces of
radish this might be the only place in
the world I've ever had valet
noodles that was awesome oh and how
convenient is that straight from the
parking garage straight to your car our
valet noodles okay we're off to the next
[Music]
place we're kind of in the back streets
of Soul within an industrial area lots
of mechanic shops around here lots of
warehouses and uh import export shops
you can this is the type of area in Sol
where you can find basically anything
you're looking for from clothes to
Plumbing okay thank
[Music]
you welcome
to O that's the name of the restaurant
and it's a classic it's a legendary
restaurant that dates back to
1946 and the main grilled Korean
barbecue that they serve here is called
Bogi bull means fire GOI means meat so
it's actually fire meat and this method
of cooking has been in Korea for
hundreds thousands of years it has a
history it's been called by different
names and I mean it one of the main
signature facts about the meat is that
it's sliced thin it's marinated before
it's grilled you can see it's really
thin slices maybe Sirin or brisket which
is thin slices marinated usually it's
quite on the sweet side we'll have to
test this out and see uh but I love the
grill shape it's a it's a dome shape
with little holes with the burner on the
bottom so that all the heat rises and
then the juices are going to spill to
the to the sides into the water so she
drills it up for your taable side kind
of like keeps scooping it onto the top
putting it on the top letting the juices
of the booi drain down into the broth
into the trough below till it kind of
caramelize and Crispies you can I mean
you can actually hear it hissing
caramelizing from that that sweet
marinade and now she turns off the fire
she says it's ready to eat that smells
so good so the method of eating this Boi
grabb a lettuce into your palm garlic
dip it into the fermented bean paste
into your lettuce and Boi oh
yeah oh
man it's so
tender and just the caramalized
sweetness contrasted by the pungency of
the garlic and the really salty bean
paste all that together in your
mouth it's so tasty that was really
really good thoroughly enjoyed it and
also I mean this restaurant is just a
preservation of traditional Korean food
Heritage especially famous for their boo
G that was so
[Music]
good oh we've been in Soul for the last
two nights upon arrival to South Korea
uh but we had a full day of eating today
and now we are
driving uh on the road trip starting the
road trip heading south uh first
destination is a place called yesan this
evening and it's going to be about a
2hour drive where we're going to have
some more food so we're on our
[Music]
way and so we made it to the town of yan
it's actually quite a beautiful
town
and we're here especially to check out
the Yan daily Market the Central Market
of the town where they're famous for
food and especially one dish that we
absolutely have to try to eat your
dinner that's the name of the dish that
we came to Yan to eat it's a chili
specialty chili chicken dish and we're
going to have an honor to see the
process of how they make
it
so the technique of cooking it is he
first stir fries the dry chilies and the
leaks in some
oil drops in the chicken really stir
fries that
up
wow gives it the walk the walk Smoky
Aroma then drenches it in the sauce
which you can tell has a lot of chilies
smell the aroma of that and then the
chicken is going to braze now for about
5 to 10 minutes um until all of that SAU
sauce starts to to dehydrate and dry in
case onto the chicken but that's a nice
technique cuz it's going to build the
layers of the flavor for the chicken oh
this is the TU the rice rice cakes U
more
leaks go
in he waits until that sauce thickens
because it's probably some sugar in the
sauce it starts to caramelize you smell
that caramelization happening um until
it thickens he waits for the precise
moment grabs a huge handful of the
chopped green chilies onto a PL plate
directly
in gives it a couple toss turns off the
fire and that's it it's
ready presenting to you the dish of the
night the chicken the Chili
Peppers going in for my first bite the
legendary chicken from chili chicken
from Yan
Market
oh wow that's so tasty oh man it's like
juicy a little bit sweet a little bit
spicy such a Harmony and a balance of
flavor Al together with the smokiness of
the walk then the breeed effect that
like ensures that all the sauce gets
absorbed into the
chicken I'm going to take another piece
of the chicken onto my rice that sauce
at the bottom is so
good
oh
wow I'd be happy to eat this dish even
without the chicken just with the
chilies and the
sauce combination of chicken chilies
fire pepper paste and fire to bring it
all together dinner at yesan Market was
delicious we drove about a 30 minute
drive we're in a small town here uh
where we checked into our hotel and I
just download all the footage from today
charge up all the batteries that's what
I do every night in the hotel oh yeah
time to charge up all of the gear every
night download everything for the next
day we're going to have to wake up quite
early in the morning and then we'll
leave by 6:00 a.m. it's a 2-hour drive
to get to the experience going to say
good night here and see you in the
morning
we just arrived to changan Village oh
they're digging the hole right now
oh they're getting started right now as
we
arrive and today we are going to cook
one of the most unique Korean meals in
an underground
steamer you can see how big this hole
is okay I think that's I think that's
the main hole but this is the strategy
here they have kind of a a circular main
hole almost the size of a hot tub and
then over here there's kind of a side
Channel with a little engraving here
because this is going to be underground
oven but also a steamer one of the most
important things is the steamer
okay oh they're still stacking loading
on logs it's going to be a bonfire oh
man with the amount of wood and logs
that they're adding to this fire it's
about to be a massive
Blaze oh man that fire it's blazing hot
you can feel the heat radiating off the
fire oh and you can see he's stacking
here a little a little opening water
water what a s
oh ah so they're building like a little
door Archway to the
oven we've moved inside to the kitchen
where they are going to load the pot
with the ingredients that's going to
steam so you got some sweet potatoes
some regular potatoes some eggs some
pumpkin some corn and some pork belly
and I mean these would all be
ingredients that they would be able to
grow that they would Harvest that would
they would raise right here within the
village so they're going to pack pack
the pot
now finish okay finished ready ready to
go okay
this is why I love to travel for food it
just offers so much insights into the
culture the history it's incredible and
so as it turns out this area they are
known for making hemp clothing
especially traditionally and they would
make their traditional clothes out of
hemp and in order to process the hemp
they would need to steam it and so they
set up these rock pits uh with hot rocks
they would steam the hemp and then you
know might as well make use of the heat
so they would put food into big pots uh
stick it onto the side of the hemp
Steamers and the using as a result of
those hot rocks and the steam that they
were using to process the hemp fiber to
make clothes they would cook a meal and
share it together with the community and
so I mean everything has a purpose and
that's also why I mean along with being
extremely laborous uh taking a lot of
effort and time it's also a lost dying
art
because they no longer process uh hemp
fiber to make clothes like that
anymore oh now he's working fast oh you
can see all that steam coming
out oh and immediately gravel soil goes
on top covering it up this is incredible
all for that pot of
food it's the the big surprise
oh
go whoa it's so hot it's still so hot
down
there here it is the reveal yeah one two
three okay one two three one two
three wow wow that smells so good M he
opens up the lid that Aroma that steam
smells so good looks like it was a
success today everything looks like it's
[Music]
cooked that pork literally as she was
slicing it you could just see the juices
pouring out of it it's it will make your
mouth water so get a piece of the pork
belly Ah that's what you do put it onto
your plate take a little bit of the a
little bit it's very salty I think a
little bit of the
shrimp might even be too much
okay wow
sweet smokey smokey smokey sweet come
some oh
wow that pork is even better than I was
expecting it tastes like straight
barbecue melt in your mouth the
smokiness is just embedded into the
fibers and muscle tissue of that pork
belly and then again the pork belly is
not it's not uh salty it's just Smoky
and then when you add that fermented
shrimp paste that gives it the saltiness
oh that pork is
insane it's just exceeded my
expectations and then I was mentioning
that I was a little bit like I mean
there were no there was no seasoning not
even salt on the ingredients but I
should have known with all the Korean
side dishes that just just totally
magnified the flavor of everything
making it just an unbelievable meal but
the day is not over yet we are still
continuing We are continuing with this
road trip in South Korea we're going to
drive about an hour to another very
famous city was there called Junu uh for
their signature dish for something that
another dish that they invented
there welcome to chanu and this is a
historical town in South Korea 8 years
ago ying and I spent almost 10 days in
chanchu we made some old videos back
then so it's great to finally be back
but we're not going to stay for long we
came here mainly just to eat one dish
one of the most important foods in all
of junju and we're at one of the
original places this is just a one meal
stop though here welcome to huk jip this
is one of the most famous probably one
of the most legendary iconic restaurants
in all of Junu and they serve a dish
that is also the most famous iconic dish
of Janu which is called Janu biop which
is mixed rice and if you look around I
mean this is almost a museum of a
restaurant they have photos they have
antiques they have traditional plaques
they've won many awards as a traditional
restaurant as a native chunchu food
restaurant and of course you come here
for the biing
Bop we're going to start with the
original Chu Bop you have all the
beautiful toppings but you have to
destroy it by mixing it all completely
oh and and there's I I I do uh Junu is
also famous for bean sprouts so there
are bean sprouts on here although they
were hidden um you mix it you got to
fully mix everything with the rice below
you want every bite to be completely
mixed in with the same amount of
ingredients an even
coating
M oh
yes it's a Harmony the sesame oil the
sweet chili guch Chong paste and the
fermentation all those chewy vegetables
the bean sprouts in particular have a
really nice kind of leathery chewy
texture the mushrooms in there the
shiaka mushrooms there's a little bit of
a a fermented flavor as well but not
overpowering just kind of adding to the
harmony of the mixture it's hot yeah
it's refreshing it's a mix It's a
combination of so many different things
everything serving a purpose everything
coming together in one
ball bi was excellent from here we are
driving it's going to be about an hour
drive to get to this it's an actual Farm
where they specialize in this spicy
Korean dish cooked over a raging
fire and what is it what is it
called wo since
1897 so this is a special for
Korean beverage for helping you digest
who oh no it's really really
sudsy it's really carbonated that's
okay oh it's
okay okay
and and apparently this is the the
ultimate beverage for helping you digest
so after all the food this is what you
need when you're in
Korea oh a little bit medicinal tasting
but kind of sweet foamy
good oh yeah kind of tastes like Red
Bull at the same
time Red Bull digestive we'll need this
as we keep on eating we have another
meal to go to
tonight it was about an hour drive and
we made it here this place is a place
I've just been so excited to come to on
this Korea trip it's in the middle of
the countryside surrounded by farms and
mountains it's a beautiful area it's
called samori Nan and so it's called
samori
Farm
wow that's a lot of heat what a process
this is straight up pyromaniac
cooking oh that's Sizzle and here
comes once the fire is going he pours
all of the sauce and the chicken which
is pre-made into the iron skillet and
it's their own secret recipe But it
includes carrots potatoes chicken and
then lots of guch Chang which is the
Korean pepper
paste they have their own secret blend
of ingredients and spices that goes into
it then it's going to sizzle for a while
as the sauces mingle and uh start to
condense and start to thicken um and I
know he's going to blow torch it more
and he might add in some more
ingredients as
well then they're going to add in some
more vegetables and let that continue to
sizzle but this is such a cool cooking
process our pan is well underway I think
it has to simmer for almost 30 minutes
to get that consistency right so that
the sauce starts to thicken and coat
onto the pieces of
chicken one of the hottest boiled lava
dishes you might ever see on earth going
in oh man for the drumstick since it's
right on top but look at the way the
sauce has just caramelized it's
thickened it's so sticky it wasn't
boiling it was bubbling going in cannot
wait it's still it's still on
fire
oh wow oh the flavor is incredible sweet
salty a little bit spicy and just
condensed flavor and just the incredible
smokiness from that fire oh man there's
something that only there's this unique
flavor that only an extreme heat can
provide oh I feel
good oh
wow I'm blown away that was is
outstanding I'm going to say that's one
of the most addictive Korean foods I've
ever had first of all so much fun to
watch being cooked prepared it's an
entertaining meal second of all you get
to sit in these incredible tents with
picnic tables and just hang out and eat
and third of all it just is so tasty uh
what a meal what an experience it's
worth it to drive all the way here to
come to this Farm to
eat
after that chicken we drove I think just
about 30 minutes we made it to the town
which is called guangju which is
actually one of the bigger cities in
Korea one of the top five bigger cities
uh but we are checking into the hotel
it's been a long day but one of the
greatest days of Korean food that I've
had but going to going to get some rest
that's going to be it for today and then
tomorrow we have another big day of food
ahead of
us we we are beginning at the yangdong
market this is one of the biggest
markets in this entire region of South
Korea one of the most popular things to
eat at the market is not seafood at
all oh man they have all the walks going
full of oil the aroma of the Fried
Chicken fills this entire Lane and this
place that we're going to it's legendary
I mean it's been featured in so many TV
shows so many celebrities have visited
but they're legendary for their whole
fried chicken Korean Fried
Chicken the first step is of course the
raw chicken and making the batter and
they make it by the batch it's
approximately I think one full chicken
and they make they don't have like this
master giant batter she mixes up the
batter for every batch of chicken and
they said that they have this magic
powder which is the seasoning which
includes a variety of different things
that's their secret seasoning that
cannot be replicated that you can only
get here so that's definitely one of the
secrets what makes their Korean Fried
Chicken different from anywhere else so
they're just continuously frying chicken
it's quite a heavy batter actually quite
a thick sticky batter and then that goes
into the the hot oil they kind of just
uh spread it out throughout the oil and
then they really like make sure each
piece doesn't stick together making sure
that oil is perfectly hot and then they
just monitor it perfectly until it's
golden brown crispy that smells
incredible and they even test it with
this huge knife chest to make sure the
chicken is perfectly cooked on the
inside even do a little bit of a moving
from one pan to the next kind of for
that double deep fry and one of the
secrets or one of the reasons uh it's
different from any other Fried Chicken
in Korea is that they use pure cotton
seed oil for deep
frying that is a huge plate of fried
chicken
yeah I'm just going to grab this piece
man you can just feel it in your fingers
how crispy it is okay here we go first
[Applause]
bite
oh
oh feels like it's still boiling in the
oil it's so hot and fresh M and it's so
crispy yeah because of that heavy batter
the magic
seasoning so crispy so perfectly golden
the chicken remains yeah very moist on
the inside even though this is the the
chicken breast and something you'll
notice is that the batter is actually
not that salty I think that's because
they they provide you salt on the side
they provide you some sauce on the side
even for the the original
version oh
man it really is some of the crispiest
chicken you'll ever have that batter the
perfect way that they fry it so crispy
on our way to the next place yeah it's
going to be about an hour drive I think
got this massive coffee
wow that's hot
[Music]
okay here we are in the south of South
Korea the area is called mu and we're
along a road which is called Montan
which is quite legendary because this is
the number one place that's known for
hay
barbecue Korean barbecue and they so
they Grill pieces of pork belly over hay
roasting them giving it a unique
fragrance and a scorched Aroma in a
grill the hay is lit on fire and it
burns so hot oh that's why it I mean
that's the benefit of the hay is it
burns so incredibly hot you can
literally instantaneously hear the
crackle look at that
Blaze
oh wow that's on literally it's pork on
fire man that's an insane amount of heat
wow and the aroma that comes off of it
it takes less than 50 seconds to cook
and you just immediately hear that
crackle all of that pork belly just
sizzling over that insanely hot
heat wow that's amazing what a process
another Korean pyromaniac
food
wow that is a hot
fire
wow and
ready
I cannot wait to try
it that is
crispy
Smokey completely melts in your mouth
the fat has just rendered and just
reacted with that flame to create this
Sensational smokiness in your
mouth oh that's so good and they do have
some combinations written on the wall
for you to try they specifically want
you to try the pork belly dipped into
their special uh Patty crab sauce oh
it's kind of thick put into the lettuce
then you add some of the onion
kimchi to the
bite oh
wow that brings out the flavor potential
so the onion is so juicy the incredible
smokiness of the pork belly and then
that sauce definitely has this fermented
seafoody crabby flavor to it but that
contrasts the also adds the saltiness
that adds to complement everything and
the acidity of the the onion kimchi oh
what a combination oh that's so good
that's so many flavors going on in your
mouth all at
once that was tasty there's no doubt
this is a gem of Korean food in the
countryside well worth making the effort
and the journey to get here just a quick
update on this ultimate South Korean
road trip we started in Soul we made our
way down the West Coast we are now in
the very southwest corner of South Korea
and from here we are going to continue
with this road trip on to the East and
we're driving to the east we're on our
way to a place called masan which is
just outside of Busan for the next Food
where they invented something very
[Music]
special
we specifically came to this city to eat
a dish that originated right here and
they make it from one of the oddest most
bizarre fish on
earth we found the whole monk fish I
mean it literally is just like a almost
like a piece of blubber with eyes coming
out of
it so we're in the kitchen we're going
to see some of the cooking process with
Auntie who is hilarious the aui gim is
made in this red caramelized pot uh the
boiling pots for the steaming and the
steaming and the boiling and then this
pot is for the the blee the blee with
the monk fish and so for the auu Jim it
includes all these seasoning powders
which she mixes up in that caramelized
pot with chili there's a little bit of
what looks like a starch or a flour and
a bunch of seasoning secret powders that
she uses mixes set up with some
scallions with some other herbs then the
The Boiled monk fish which he boils for
probably 15 minutes or so and plus that
small mountain of bean sprouts uh then
she just tosses that up mixes it on a
low heat uh and that's the that's the
main aim the main dish this is the
original the classic the sang Akim and
it has the mfish in it plus a small
mountain of bean sprouts some of the
longest bean sprouts I've ever seen in
my life okay let's start with this piece
of monkfish I got a nice nugget of the
monkfish for my my first bite I can't
wait this is my first time to ever try
this
dish oh
wow
M oh that's incredible the meat of the
monkfish is so meaty you could almost
think that it's chicken like a really
soft fluffy chicken and then often times
when you get this red sauce it can be
kind of on the sweeter side sometimes
this one is not it's not sweet it's just
salty a little bit spicy and just
magnifies the spongy fluffiness of that
monk fish what a dish I mean from the
moment I saw her in the kitchen I knew
you could trust her with all of your
monkfish needs and
desires man that's so tasty the
combination those bean sprouts are
incredible oh man this has now become
one of my favorite Korean dishes I can't
believe I've never had this one before
my first time I'm in love with it oh
what a
dish that was outstanding so flavorful
so tasty spicy and Auntie making it
she's just the queen of auu Jim of
monkfish she is a legend so cool what a
meal what a spot highly recommend it and
you can eat this dish all over Korea I
know for sure you can find it in Soul
but just coming to the location where it
originates where it's the most popular
where it came from gives it even more
[Music]
meaning
and today we're going on an ultimate
Korean street food tour to eat some of
the best local food in Busan starting
right here at tagachi Market which is
the biggest seafood market in all of
South
[Music]
Korea he's doing a beautiful job with
that plate of fresh SE bre Sashimi that
is oh man the transparency the color of
that fish is beautiful
those spotted sardines that's just
incredible he cleans them so well takes
out the center bone dries them makes
sure they're really dry with a towel and
then he just slices them finally almost
like a like a slicing machine so thin
slices oh man that's going to be so good
and that's what we're going to eat for
for sashimi oh and he's doing a variety
of techniques well I love all sorts of
fish but sometimes small fish are some
of the tastiest best fish uh that you
can possibly eat so I'm I'm really
excited to try
this oh nice
come here we are beginning this Busan
food tour Ultra fresh seafood I cannot
wait to start digging into that sashimi
and look at the way he made this floral
formation of the Sashimi of the bream
transparent slices so white and then it
is called H which is the the raw raw
form of fish or raw form of of
ingredients um this would be the the
bean sauce that you could dip into with
garlic looks like there's some green
chilies in there as
well little dab in this
oh wow oh that's
fresh the texture the muscle it melts in
your mouth and it has a little bit of
chew at the same time what a just Ultra
Clean Fish and we also have the the
seasonal specialty which are the boded
sardines a
delicacy because it has little bones in
it it has this little bit of a crunch
trip but the way you sliced it you can
just crunch through the bones giving it
extra texture almost has a little
buttery feel to it with that crunch oh
that's so
good we're going to continue eating we
have another place to eat that's
actually at the fish
market the next place we're going is
down this alley there's so many signs on
this alley So Many
[Music]
Colors
this is a famous place for old school
for their uh intestines barbecue as well
as their triped hot
pot this the
who that's the
intestine wow that's a whole
coil oh man there's
wording so
oily oh oh so it's first griddle fried
and then onto the Hot
Grill so it's a two-step cooking process
oh it Squirts and
sprays okay we're moving into the this
small
intestines this is when things are
really getting excited the the
intestines oh intestines are always just
slightly hilarious and delicious
delicacy and I mean just the way they
look and the way they're so fatty
they're just spewing with juices and as
she adds it to the fire they just erupt
with flame another dip into the
sauce oh
wow oh that's so
good almost has a Nutty creaminess to it
with a Chey wrapper and the smokiness
grilled in its own fat on the gdle then
the smokiness from the grill to tar off
all of that excess oil and grease
intestines is fantastic yes and then
they also we also have those they look
like sausages but they're the big
intestines sometimes I've heard them
called flower intestines because when
you chop them open they just kind of
spew with fat and juices into a floral
floral crystals almost okay here we go
let's try the flower
Ines
oh that's like fat on
fire oh that totally melts in your mouth
oh man it liquefies then with that kind
of stretchy skin around it flower fat on
the inside just totally dissolves on
your tongue oh that was satisfying that
was a a textural playground in your
mouth and I just absolutely love the
history here and the
culture
[Music]
from here we are heading back to the
center of Busan where we're going to go
to another market and try some street
food
[Music]
snacks we are at G shiang Market this is
one of the extremely popular Market
areas and actually connected I mean
basically this whole Central area of
Busan is a market connected to the fish
market where we at this morning but
there's a lot of things you could buy
here lots of fashion accessories
but there is some street food to be
found including a couple of famous
things that we got to try when we're
here yeah it's so another one of the
popular street foods that you have to
try when you come to Busan is called
Busan omuk it's fish cake boiling on
sticks and it's what's awesome is it's
self-service you grab your own let's do
it sticks this one is I think the most
classic huge sheet of fish cake okay dip
oh that looks extremely
spongy oh
yeah almost feels like fish tofu well
really spongy just absorbs all of that
broth as it soaks boils remain remains
hot nice
texture and then also probably one of
the coolest moves of all you grab a red
cup and it's a scooper cup then you can
just dip into that
broth just no double
dipping a little bit
salty not overly powerful in flavor kind
of mild watery salty and just with that
Essence that Aroma of the fish
broth there's an entire Lane for
something which is called bingu which
you might have heard of it's one of the
most famous Korean desserts a shave ice
but with so many
toppings oh shaved ice beans fruit oh
more ice gets shaved
on condensed milk that's condensed milk
goes
on oh and what's that go on top some
candied
fruits
oh oh yeah oh that is refreshing I
think The Joy of Eating bingu is that
when it starts to melt it starts to
create these new flavors and mix all the
ingredients together you've got the
texture of that ice which is it's shaved
so fine that it has a little crunch but
as soon as you crunch down it just melts
dissolves on your tongue the beans are a
little bit sweet and just act to to to
bring it together and then you got that
candy fruit and the condensed milk which
also just makes it
milky
the Bing Su was excellent very
refreshing and just a simple simple Bing
suo which is what I enjoy okay we're on
our way to find another
[Music]
thing in order to make it she takes a
handful of the dough which is quite
sticky uh she kind of presses it into a
ball and then she puts in a spoonful of
this cinnamon sugar mixture and then
wraps it up to close it then she puts it
onto the hot griddle which there's oil
in it to shallow fry he shallow fries it
in the oil smashes it down into a Patty
formation and then flips it over and
Cooks it until it's golden brown until
the the sugar starts to melt on the
inside and then the really cool move is
that once it's done and crispy they make
an incision into the top of it and load
it up with a a bunch of uh crushed I
think almonds and pumpkin seeds nuts a
variety of nuts on the inside and then
it's ready to eat a handheld pocket
that's a really really cool idea and and
serve it to you in a cup check this out
I mean it was good it was good already
before the nuts but when they open it up
and load it full of nuts that makes it
even better oh there's even uh I think
almonds pumpkin seeds and sunflower
seeds at least maybe more and that's hot
that's right out of the
oil oh man it's good crispy on the
outside the the dough is really chewy
elasticy you got the sweetness of the
sugar which has been melted with the
cinnamon and then the crunch of the nuts
the nuttiness of it oh all coming
together kind of like a doughnut pocket
but so good that was a great time
definitely a place you want to get lost
just walking around exploring all the
shopping alleys and lots of street food
tucked
[Music]
within we ended up drying giving
probably a 15-minute drive or so from
where we were uh to a place called Aman
Park and this is on the seaside actually
it's really popular for fishing almost
everyone here is fishing but it's also
popular for these local Busan food
tents we are in and this type of dining
is called the poang MAA it's a part of
the Busan Korean food culture it's like
this hot steamy tent and you feel all
the heat coming from all the grills
going clouds of smoke Rising as you
grill up Seafood um and they're
especially known for having some drinks
having some bites to eat some snacks
some grilling some seafood and for the
the loud environment what a what an
atmosphere oh wow this is literally a
party
tray I see spaghetti I see hamburgers I
see shrimp I see Abalone all on this
tray and it's kind of like you there's
no real menu you kind of just serve you
they have these set menus that you order
and we got the definitely the party
platter here comes the
fire put it on to the to the edge okay
oh the the scallops all of them
y take a blob a block of butter put one
into put one into each scallop and then
you add a little cheese yeah you can try
like cover it up with cheese make it
like uh cover with cheese okay cover it
with
cheese oh man yes
yes melted cheese and
butter that's a raging hot fire it's a
raging hot fire okay I think this one is
ready though cheese onions scallop has
come off woo okay let's go right off the
grill in the fire
oh
wow the cheese is so mild but you got
the sweetness of the scallop the onions
the green pepper in there the fire this
red cheesy
shrimpy just melting sauce molten lava
cheese it looks like
literally molten hot lava
cheese maybe with pepper paste and trimp
in the
center oh wow again that was the by far
the sweatiest Korean meal I've ever had
this is such a popular place so local
and yet so modern so much cheesee but
man it's so Smoky so hot back there just
feels great to be back in the fresh air
and what a day in
Busan we drove a little bit outside of
town about 15 20 minutes and we are at a
legendary place to eat one of the
signature noodles that originates right
here in Busan I love Korean noodles I'm
very excited this entire restaurant
specializes in something called Milan
which is uh busan's special noodle this
is a beautiful noodle dish and you can
see that the noodles are yellow in color
they're made from wheat flour and two
different versions uh one is the I think
the original one is with ice water soup
which I have grown to absolutely love so
actually they don't serve you any spoons
there were no spoons in the in the
little little case so I think you're
supposed to drink the
broth
oh oh oh wow the initial first taste is
a little bit sweet not too salty and
then you get this slushy this like beefy
slushie in your mouth all at the same
time oh it's so refreshing oh I love it
so you're going to mix it up first mix
up the the ball of noodles oh that's a
it's a nice tight wad of noodles and you
can see all that GOI Chong mixing into
the icy broth cucumbers daon radish
pieces of slices of beef ice let's try
those
noodles
mhm oh yes the texture of those noodles
is incredible slightly
chewy so clean so pure tasting the
sweetness from the goou Chong the icy
coldness the beefiness man those are
quality noodles you can taste that
they're just like real deal handmade
noodles I love
that
mhm so
refreshing I like them both but I really
like the one with the icy water then
really good shreds of shreds of beef
[Music]
radish
that was excellent I especially again
love the one with the icy cold noodles
the
slushie welcome to the city of teu and
teu is the third largest city in South
Korea we just this morning drove from
Busan to the city of teu we came here
specifically to eat a couple of foods
that are originate that come from here
and that are most popular here and the
first dish that we're going to go eat
right now is called Jim galby it's this
spicy ribs stew
and I'm really looking forward to eating
it can't wait to try
it this is the normal version normal
version yeah on as soon as you order it
comes out record fast so fast because I
think it's a dish that takes a long time
to cook and so they probably have it
already prepared stewed down brazed
together with all of those chilies and
all of those spices until it comes
together so it takes a long times they
probably just scoop it out into the bowl
and one of the signatures about this
dish is that it's always served in this
nickel silver bowl which apparently from
what I was reading is not only for looks
and not only for presentation but it
actually contributes to the flavor so
I'm going to try the I'm going to try
the normal version First and these are
Korean short ribs yeah look at how much
garlic is just taped up on there it's
basically garlic just garlic wow this
version that I'm going to taste first is
with American beef and then the the
version in this this uh case this brown
wooden case is with Korean beef and then
on top of that the American beef we got
as the normal normal spicy typical spicy
but the Korean beef we got the extra
spicy version so I'll try American beef
normal spicy version First
plain oh wow what a dish that beef of
the ribs just melts in your mouth it's
so so tender oh man often times when you
have G um
barbecue it's fatty and really really
flavorful but it has this kind of a
chewiness to it this muscly chewiness to
it this they brazed it down until it
just falls off the bone it's so tender
let's try the Korean
beef I'm digging into the extra spicy
and coat it in that
sauce grab a grab another
rib oh oh it keeps on coming
keeps on
coming
beautiful when it's hanging like this
there's only way to it's you can only go
in
vertically oh wow that is so tender all
the Korean beef m
oh the extra spicy oh the
garlic and the extra spicy okay you do
notice that it's a bit it's a bit
spicier definitely spicier than the
original but still not not overpowering
spicy at all um just a good flavor of
the red chili powder chili flakes and
massive garlic and the sweetness is not
overpowering either it's just just
Harmony of sweetness that adds to
it man that melts in your mouth okay
let's go with the the full combo
here oh that's a huge Pearl Olive look
at the size of that Pearl I'm going with
the spoon so that we can get all of that
all of that
sauce you're going to want to load it up
with as much of that sauce as
possible
garlic go go with the green chili on
this
bite
yeah oh man that's a big
one
oh that
is huge flavor might need a napkin after
that
but the chili red
sauce garlic on top of garlic chili on
top of chili perilla Leaf oh that's a
that is a
extraordinary oh man that's a my first
time to ever try this uh Korean dish
jimal from teu and it was awesomely
awesomely good that flavor is probably
going to be in my mouth for the rest of
the
day I'm in a town which is called Yong
Chan in South Korea we drove here it was
about 45 minutes from the bigger town of
U in South Korea and we spe specifically
came to this town to eat an original
version of yuk which is the Korean R
beef Tartar and they serve there's a
legendary restaurant here uh that has
been serving it for decades and it's
definitely a regional
specialty here we are at the front of
the restaurant and it's kind of on this
corner uh occupying a nice little
prominent Corner section here uh the
name it's a very interesting name how
would you pronounce it uh it's p
[Laughter]
one more
time Yong Yong yes that's good yeah okay
this is the spot I'm very
excited oh sir this is at the front of
restaurant here you can tell that this
is an all beef restaurant they have all
the fresh beef here slicing up into a
variety of different shapes and sizes
for the different dishes that they're
preparing this place is a straight up
Butchery they have all the fresh meat
they specialized in fresh hanu Korean
beef they cut the beef differently for
the different dishes that they they
serve and so the for yuk it is usually
uh a very like thin Julian of of beef
that they
use oh
nice so we got our order in and then as
soon as you make your order Within she
comes back with the stew the soup uh
because I think that's all ready to go
they just put it in and they want it to
start boiling throughout your meal so
that it starts cooking so that you can
be eating it and so that's going to boil
away we're still waiting for the the UK
which is on its
way
UK so we ended up actually I think
getting every single dish that they
offer on the menu the soup stew the blee
which is kind of grilled in a iron
Skittle but also kind of boiled I mean
it's boiled in its own juices and
marinade so it's more of a a simmered
beef dish and then the main plate the
main event the yuk Quay and this is
different from other versions that I
guess I've never had this version before
because typically I have the the common
version of ukay in South Korea which is
thinly sliced uh Julian beef like this
and then they mix it with pears with a
raw egg which you stir up and then you
you grab bites this one the texture
looks a little bit different
and it's minced up with some herbs it
looks like scallions and a lot of sesame
oil and sesame seeds and this is just
beautiful oh man you could just smell
the freshness man that texture and it's
just you can see how it's just kind of
chopped in with those
herbs
wow oh that's unbel un
believable that completely melts in your
mouth oh it's so tender it
dissolves and this
immediate like sensation of sesame oil
just fills your tongue have had UK
before around
Korea this one and often times it can be
a little bit chewy which I mean still is
really good but this one is the most
tender most melt iny mouth version I've
ever had without a doubt
wow okay the soup is fully ready cooked
I'm going to try some of the or the stew
actually I'll try some of the stew
next it's just really clean tasting it
taste a the those red chili
flakes the leaks in there the mushrooms
and then in comparison to the flavor of
the uku though it's mild it's a total
change contrast in your
mouth okay so this has been simmered
marinated simmered you can see how some
of the blood has started to curdle
there's onions in there there's
leaks so fragrant oh even
mushrooms oh man it just melts in your
mouth again it's so tender and then we
have the last dish which is
the same yuk the same raw beef tartar
except this one is served in a metal
Bowl because you're supposed to mix with
rice and mix with salad dump the whole
rice in then this bowl of salad add it
also at least some of
it so this is the yuk bi
b I kid you not that is one of the
greatest raw beefs you'll have and I
mean for sure that's the best UK Quake
I've ever had mixed with the hot rice
the salad the crunch of the salad the
freshness that gives it a whole new
dimension oh man that's
good just finished the greatest yukay
Korean yukay meal I've ever had that was
absolutely phenomenal I'm going to dream
about this one that's that's with
without a doubt uh but from here we
drive back to teu and then tomorrow
we're going to continue up the east
coast of South
Korea by the way
good morning and something that I often
try to do either in the morning or the
evening is a lot of push-ups when we're
[Applause]
traveling yes and I thought it would be
a good time to give you a quick update
on how this Korean road trip is going so
far but again we started in Soul and if
you've been following along we drove
down the west coast of South Korea uh
eating Foods along the way and then all
the way to the southwestern Corner uh
and then we drove over the across the
southern part of the peninsula onto
Busan and then yesterday we drove up to
teu where we ate some Delicacies I've
learned so much and really gained much
more of an understanding of the regional
variations of Korean cuisine as well as
the possibility the diversity of the
possibility of dishes that are available
I mean this is the reason that I I love
to travel for food and I love to get off
the beaten path from here today we drive
up the east coast of the Korean
Peninsula up to a city called so Cho
which is in the very Northeastern corner
it's famous for seafood and especially
Red Snow Crabs so we're going to go on a
food tour today of Soo but it's going to
be a long drive to get
there
we've been driving for about 3 hours
made one or two stops uh bathroom stops
along the way and we drove through the
mountains really rugged really beautiful
scenery Mountain scenery and now we came
down dropped in elevation to the
coastline and from here we will be going
up the coast poast to soo I think we
have about 45 minutes an hour left uh
until we reach our destination where we
are going to begin a Soo food
tour Soo is known for its seafood and I
mean that's really the reason I wanted
to come here we're beginning this food
tour at the central tourist Market where
some of the Korean street foods here are
not seafood at all and they're one of
the most popular things to eat in all of
Soo
nice this Market is full of all sorts of
things from street food snacks to fresh
raw ingredients so it's all I mean
walking streets here and we are now
going down one of the main alleys of the
market here we are we found it it is
white and
bright almost to the point where you
need sunglasses but from what I
understand people will travel from Soul
and around the country here just to eat
what they serve right here in Soo let's
open the the gift it is a straight up
gift ready for the reveal here let's see
open it up
oh not a reveal let's open it up again
wow fancy packaging here we go I think
this might be the real reveal let's
go there it is wow this is one of the
most popular things to eat in all of so
fried chicken nuggets of fried chicken
in this Sweet Sticky sauce with almonds
with green chilies smells really good
and served in a Christmas gift box let's
try it out wow it's sticky sauce is
really
[Applause]
sticky oh
wow that's
tasty
M okay it is sweet definitely
sweet but it has this incredible
saltiness the sauce is so s sticky and I
think it's so garlicky that's like
straight up garlic fried chicken m and
even though it's cold or room
temperature and sort of the sauce has
absorbed into this crispy breading which
kind of seems ironic for fried chicken
that actually is part of the the
attraction it just absorbs that sauce
into that crispy
batter this is another extremely popular
food item that people come to soo just
to eat and we got off one of the alleys
from the main market and this is the
place we're coming to try it
out okay those are the dipping sauces oh
nice oh the squid tnd comes on a
sizzling Skillet oh that's beautiful it
is a whole squid stuffed fried egg
battered and on a sizzling
platter I'm going to go in for the squid
tday what a fantastic brilliant idea you
can see the squid is the exterior it's
the wrapper of the sausage stuffed with
rice stuffed with maybe scallions and
some other
things so you take this
bite oh it's good I mean it's just just
such a wonderful natural thing to do
with Squid stuff it with even more
[Music]
deliciousness about a 10-minute drive
away is the next market and this Market
is known for its red snow crabs
especially the east coast of Korea
you'll find tons and tons of red snow
crabs one of the prizes of the sea and
as you can see up there this cluster is
known for their seafood and especially
their crabs so we're going to walk
around we're going to see some of the
market and then we are definitely going
to try some
[Music]
crab got to admit the sea squirt is not
my favorite item from the sea they're
just so Briny so salty but we got to
give it a try every time we have a have
the
opportunity oh man that sea squirt was
that was intense it has this bitterness
to it you almost feel this ammonia
coming out of it almost goes up your
brain a little bit that is unique
definitely an advanced
Seafood he's finding us three of the
best Soo snow crabs so we're going to
have the full Soo red snow crab
meal immediately into the steaming
containers okay and that's the steamer
right there wow that's fast straight
from the tank straight to the steamer on
the sidewalk right here
okay oh they serve it to you hole like
that
okay
and what he's doing is he's taking all
those leg and he's just taking the knife
and just slicing down that shell look
how that's how soft the shell is he
could just slice that knife so we've got
the whole crab sculpture here we also
have just the whole crab which he's
going to show us how to cut up and eat
first
okay
yeah so scissors and again that shell is
so soft cuts off one of the legs oh
that's the claw actually oh and that
just pops out the meat just pops
out here's one of the ones that he poked
through using its own shell it's kind of
like one of those pop ice when you poke
that stick through the the ice and keep
popping it up except
crab
M
wow oh it's so juicy too and such a
silky texture that is outstanding flavor
so silky buttery just melts in your
mouth mooving to try that
claw and when you dip it into the tamali
that that row head butter gives it a
little bit of a more complexity like a
little bit of a
bitterness
oh
man that is so just sweet almost syrupy
sweet it's so sweet naturally the claw
as usual has a different texture more
fibrous more stringy oh man I thought we
had already reached the Pinnacle of crab
but they took it to the next level but
the entire snow crab in a bowl of Raman
this is another one of their Specialties
right here oh what a genius idea that
broth the aroma all of the shell boiled
in the
soup wow salty sweet from the crab some
of those
noodles one another
just totally awesome usage of the snow
crab oh what a
meal some people might come to so Cho
for that Fried Chicken but I can
guarantee you I'll be coming back for
the red snow crab and that was by far
the Highlight that it's so good
everything about that restaurant the
experience was so good straight up
[Music]
Gourmet good morning from Soo and we
ended up driving a little bit into the
mountain so when you come to soo there
known for the sea they're known for
their crabs but they're also really
known for their mountains in the summer
and in the winter when you can go
snowing on the Peaks and Hiking uh and
we stayed at a hotel which was in the in
the mountain area woke up this morning
to the beautiful fresh air uh the nature
here is spectacular but this morning we
are uh about ready to head back to se
and it's going to be about a 2 to three
hour drive I think to get back to
Soul
sh
okay welcome back to
Soul
ah and we have three restaurants to go
to today and these are some of we're
going to be eating some of a few of my
favorite Korean dishes which we haven't
tried yet on this trip a dish that is
probably the most soothing dish in all
of Korea it has medicinal benefits it's
just so good that's the
place we came here to specifically eat
the dish which is called sang which is a
jinang chicken soup and usually includes
a whole spring chicken or a young
chicken in a hot Earth and wear Bowl
which has just been boiled simmered the
bones uh stuffed with rice and ginsing
and it's so good
oh the sunflower seed oh the thickness
of the skin and the chicken just boiled
down all of that the juices and the oils
the ginang oh it's so good and then you
can see that it's an entire chicken
stuffed with a combination of
jinsang spices and rice on the inside oh
all that entire then carcass just lifts
off like a lid and you can see nestled
inside of there oh whole clothes of
garlic rice is that a water chestnut I
think oh beautiful oh man I'm going to
scoop that out oh and you can smell the
richness of the chicken fat all just
converging onto that that
Center okay don't take a giant bite out
of the the crevice of the
chicken it's still on fire oh yeah but
but so good the rice just melts in your
mouth you really taste the flavor of the
Gin Tang in the cavity oh that's so good
the way it literally just pulls apart
from the bone complete
effortlessness has to be the easiest
chicken whole chicken to eat on
Earth that was so good and you can
actually literally feel your body the
internal heat of your body Rising after
you eat that dish oh it's so soothing so
comforting oh that was
good this is the spot let's eat
gamjatang well this is a small little
restaurant just with four tables uh but
she's been serving for 38 years and
specializing in gatang which is one of
the great Korean
dishes we ordered the biggest size and
she's going to make it now oh here it is
that's one of the main components that
you AB we have to have the pork bones or
the side bones or the back
bones and those are the outer leaves of
the Cabbage potatoes red chili powder I
think that's crushed up Pilla seeds
perilla seeds and now over to the broth
station broth is already reding color
from all the all the spices and the
chili that she probably
adds you have a hot pot at your table so
that it can boil away and start to keep
on cooking and heat up and bring all the
ingredients together at your table
oh what a dish and I do remember ying
and I had this dish I think we just kind
of stumbled onto it first trip to Korea
many many years ago and ever since that
trip it's been one of our our go-to
dishes one of the the greatest of all
Korean foods here we
go oh that pork is so tender completely
melts in your mouth M come to again one
of the great Korean dishes but her
version is incredible so good and you
can tell her passion for it she just
does it so well that just has all the
right things that you want juicy tender
pork chewy fragrant cabbage leaves Pilla
seed leaves Chili
[Music]
Pepper now we're on our way to one more
place for barbecue today place I was
really looking forward to it's the
standing barrel barbecue really old
school style uh with a place with a lot
of history and
Heritage we are in mdong now mdong is
one of the most popular walking shopping
districts in Olive Soul always busy
crowded and we are going to a place
that's called Mong Sao Cal which
specializes again in Korean short ribs
barbecue but something totally different
it's a Heritage Restaurant I can't wait
to try it this place is so cool standing
barrel barbecue all the barbecues are
with in grills there's no seats so it's
standing only but this is really one of
the again one of the original Heritage
Korean barbecue especially famous for
the C which is the the Korean short ribs
here it comes wow there it is there's
their special Cal oh and you can see
it's marinated oh that is
beautiful oh man that smells good
they're so meaty these are some of the
meatest short ribs I've ever seen
I'm already loving the look of that
marinade looks like garlic lots of
garlic green chilies sesame
seeds that Aroma is incredible you can
just see how juicy they're going to be
so incredibly meaty oh just they're like
flaps of meat that just come right off
the bone oh those are beauties ready to
start eating grab a piece of the the K
he said the hot the sauce is their
signature that's what sets them apart
this might be the coolest Korean
barbecue yet such a cool con
concept
wow oh it's so
tender
wow wow ohu has the jingu has the right
idea yeah you then take one of the green
chilies dip it in the goou Chong
maybe and one more essential part of
this meal experience cheers men
that that is spectacular the meat itself
is such good quality oh that might be
the best C
yet and this concept is just so perfect
huddled around a grill enjoying meat
together perfect
environment so we finished with the
standing barrel barbecue I can honestly
say that was one of the greatest K
Korean barbecue short rib mules I've
ever had then it was good and they were
really really nice oh that place highly
recommended and man that was a lot of
good food really fast in Soul today but
we're back in the parking lot now back
to the van we're going to go check into
the hotel call it a day uh yeah get some
rest get some sleep it's been another
awesome awesome
day
look at the size of that stuffed animal
it's
huge welcome back to
Soul I'm definitely ready to have a good
night sleep tonight but check this out
this time we're on the 37th floor
and okay we might need to see the view
in the morning but we have a River View
High
Above yeah going to be a really nice
view from here but I think that's going
to be all for right now good night and
see you
tomorrow good morning it's a dark rainy
drizzly day in Soul today actually we've
been blessed with really good weather
this entire trip
today it's looking like it's going to
rain for the rest of the day but we have
two restaurants to go to
today welcome to mongan this place is
extremely popular it's kind of a modern
Korean barbecue restaurant that
specializes and I've seen some of the
photos in these gigantic Dino sized
ribs cooked in a very special way
[Music]
so in order to make their special ribs
pork ribs what they do is they have the
huge ribs they bring them over into this
Grill cabinet and then he just kind of
grills them really quickly over a really
hot charcoal
fire then the trick here is using hay so
he gets a bundle of hay in his palm he
lights that on fire and then he puts the
ribs into the hay uh watching them as
they go up in a flame and just like
burst in a flame with that fat and that
oil but just like keeping really control
just for a few seconds just to embed it
with that smokiness of that burnt hay
and then flips them over so they're just
barely I think singed on the outside
they're not really cooked on the inside
yet then they go onto some serving trays
um and then that's going to go to your
table but already just infused with the
aroma of that smoke that smells
incredible oh oh it's so long it's a
huge
rib it takes up the entire
griddle oh well he SLI It Off the
Bone oh strips It Off the
[Music]
Bone oh look at the marble look at the
fat mixed within that muscle
and it really does have a different
Aroma with that infusion of the hay
smoke in it oh man this is truly magical
meat eating experience they do it all in
front of you on this massive iron hot
griddle he said to eat it as is no
sausers
by
oh oh
wow it is so tender and Spong spy and so
fatty oh man that texture is incredible
the flavor keeps on coming the smokiness
wow that's good did you guys have lunch
yeah we did okay we had Mala oh nice we
wanted something yeah home I mean
technically not home true true you guys
because we had a big breakfast at the
buffet we didn't have anything and then
it was kind of like hungry but don't
want to eat anything so no we didn't
have any
M SS good
though yeah you need like like should we
go restaurant you need a change
of we've had a lot of barbecue yeah and
a lot of go
CH we're at the next place it's called
Pro ganang gang the next dish that we're
eating on this ultimate Korean food tour
ganang gang which is the raw soy
marinated Korean crabs these are
beautiful beautiful pieces of crab just
straight up blooming blooming like ice
cream glistening golden crab
lollipop all the rich
creaminess oh it's
so so flavorful so rich has this amazing
saltiness a little bit of a sweetness
like melt in your mouth straight up crab
pudding ice cream of the
sea and it's so incredibly clean
tasting oh man this is an absolute
delicacy in Korea you know why it's
loved so much because it's so tasty it
just dissolves on your tongue and it's
cool it's refreshing and squeeze it and
the all the all it just comes out the
meat the row all comes
out the raw crab and then from there you
can keep eating it with your rice all
that flavor just coating the
rice and that contrast of the the cool
cold refreshing crab with the hot
rice oh that's good wow that is
extraordinary we have another version of
the crabs which is called yongyong getch
now these are again raw crabs this time
it's marinated in more of a a pepper
paste oh
wow oh that one is amazing oh man melt
in your mouth it's a stronger flavor
with that pepper paste with the sesame
seeds
yeah that's delicious this is the best
part and how we eat
the
head with all of the row and the juice
in there if if I go with my friends we
never ever surrender
okay like a digging digging deep
inside digging deep deep deep inside and
get everything out from the corner like
this digging every single from the
corner and then the rice oh yeah rice
into the shell oh okay rice into the
shell okay and
then like a bib and Bop style mhm okay
this is the best part and best way to
enjoy the soy crab okay best part of
Kang gang Kang gang yes and to this
moment there's no friend there's no wife
there's no family just a compete to get
it that is when you eat gangang with
your friends no more friends every man
for no brother every man for yourself
yes only for
us the greatest delicacy of the head get
all of that out of the casses oh and
this one even has the pepper paste all
within that's just straight up okay rice
goes in just mix it
up
wow absolutely phenomenal dinner gang
get Chang raw soy marinated crabs highly
recommended tomorrow we go to the
airport
good
morning on the way to the airport just a
really quick
lunch oh that's hot
oh did not want to miss sundubu jig
before leaving
Korea and I'm definitely going to have
some kimchi withdrawals and one of the
biggest lessons I learned this trip how
to eat like a real Korean Pro when you
get to the bottom of your soup tip it
over so you can get every last
drop
okay thank you very much thank you very
much here we are back at inan airport
where it all
began this time I have so much more of
an appreciation for South Korea its
people culture the different regions and
especially with Unforgettable memories
of South Korean food if you made it this
far and watched this entire Korean food
documentary first I want to say a big
thank you and I would be extremely
grateful if you would give this video a
thumbs up and if you might share it with
a friend who also loves to travel and
eat I also want to say a huge thank you
to the Korea tourism Organization kto
for making this entire trip happen and
remember when you're in South Korea try
it all